

HANA WIDYATARI

+6281321861427 | hanawidyatari@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/hana-widyatari/ | https://hana-widyatari.netlify.app/

Bandung, Indonesia

A technology and design enthusiast with experienced in website projects. Loved to explore and learn about web programming and design. Powerful tool to build the web is Javascript using React and Vue JS framework. Skilled in problem solving, designing, and managing data.

Work Experiences

Mazecare - Hongkong, SAR

Oct 2022 - Present

Software Engineer | Frontend Developer

Mazecare is a digital healthcare platform that simplifies communication between the trifecta of patient, provider, and insurer. Mazecare is a Healthcare IT Products and Services Company and builds a robust, feature-rich suite of products to deliver significant value to the stakeholders of the healthcare industry.

- Handled Developing, testing, maintaining, and improving web application for health care company.
- Translated and designing a web UI UX design into code using Vue with Nuxt Js and tailwind CSS.
- · Performed fix bugs and debugging.
- Built re-useable components for future use, increased code and clean code.
- Communicating with client for better user experience for new development features.

Radya Labs - Bandung, Indonesia

Mar 2022 - May 2022

Junior Frontend Developer

Radya Digital (formerly known as Radya Labs) is a mobile software development company. The pioneer of windows phone application development in Indonesia with good hands in developing various mobile phone platforms.

- · Made a CMS web using typescript language.
- Translated a web UI for website from UI/UX design into code using Next Js, React Js
- · Fetching API from backend to frontend using axios.
- Made the web interactive and functional using Yup, React portal, drawer, and modal.
- · Worked with version control bitbucket and Git.
- · Always delivered to strict deadlines and received positive feedback from Project Managers and clients

Ministry of Agrarian Affairs and Spatial Planing - Jakarta,

Jun 2021 - Sep 2021

Indonesia

Revalidation and Quality Control Officer

The Ministry of Agrarian and Spatial Planning, the Ministry of Agrarian and Spatial Planning (ATR) has the task of organizing government affairs in the field of agrarian / land and spatial planning to assist the President Indonesia in carrying out state governance.

- Verified the population of database in the KKP's website.
- Revalidated the digital land books database in the KKP's website based on the physic of the land books for Centre of Jakarta area.
- Added and corrected the textual mistakes from the digital land books in KKP's website.
- Weekly progress of revalidation reported by officer to the Ministry of Agrarian Affairs and Spatial Planning. Satisfied by 90% of with weekly progress that has been reported.
- Reduce mistakes digital land book 80% per-week.

PT. Inovasi Geomatika Indonesia - Bandung, Indonesia

Feb 2019 - Aug 2019

3D Model Analyst and Development Engineering

- Reconstructed laser scanner, terrestrial, and aerial photogrammetry data into 3D point cloud.
- Compiled the laser scanner, terrestrial, and photogrammetry 3D point cloud.
- Build the compiled 3D point cloud into 3D model object and justified the detail of 3D model object.
- · Created virtual reality (VR) from 3D model and attached some information about the object.

PT. Inovasi Geomatika Indonesia - Bandung, Indonesia

Jul 2018 - Aug 2018

Internship MEP and 3D Modeler

- · Built an exterior 3D modelling building with acquisition data from aerial photogrammetry using Photo-modeler.
- Built an interior 3D modelling and MEP (Mechanical Electrical and Plumbing) system from architecture building plan using ArchiCAD.
- Reported and presented the progress and final result to supervisor BIM division.

Education Level

- Build an individual website project with monolithic architecture.
- Build a team project (e-commerce and admin panel website) with micro service architecture and deployed it.
- · Learned to code using Javascript language.
- Learned to design web using basic HTML, CSS integrated with DOM (Document Object Model), ReactJS, and bootstrap framework
 as frontend side.

Aug 2015 - Aug 2019

- Learned to code with REST API and backend side using MERN (MongoDB, Express, ReactJS, Node) stack.
- Learned version control system and state management such as redux.
- Learned about testing using Jest, eslint, and CI/CD using GitHub Action.

Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember - Surabaya, Indonesia

Bachelor Degree in Geomatics Engineering, 3.58/4.00

- Geo-Innovation Bootcamp BIG 2017 National
- PKM KC national 2017 funded by DIKTI National
- Forum Commtech Integrated Initiative 2017 International

Organisational Experience

Himage Aug 2016 - Aug 2019

Member

Department organization for Geomatics Engineering Institute Technology of Sepuluh Nopember.

- Active and support all the activity for geomatics engineering department events.
- Help organization for giving suggestion and aspiration to improve the organization.

Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- Fullstack Web Developer Bootcamp: BINAR Academy **⊙** (2022):